steadfast.net 2013-06-13

# Privacy Policy | US-EU Safe Harbor Policy | Steadfast, Chicago Cloud and Data Center Services

## This document states the privacy protections you have as a client.

_Last updated: May 9, 2012_

This is the web site of **NoZone, Inc.**

Our postal address is:

725 S Wells St  
8th Floor  
Chicago, IL 60607

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@steadfast.net](mailto:support@steadfast.net) or you can reach us by telephone at 312-602-2689.

NoZone, Inc. complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. NoZone, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's hostname and IP, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used for internal review, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to contact the user as they requested, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address or calling us at the above telephone number.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address.

Please provide us with your exact name, phone number, and address. We will be sure your name is not shared with other organizations.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by calling us at the number provided above or e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, transaction information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site.

With respect to security: We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site and all sensitive information is stored in an encrypted format.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>.

## United States / EU, Swiss Safe Harbor Framework Principles

### Notice

Steadfast shall inform customers of the purpose for which it collects and uses personal information. Steadfast shall also inform the customer of any disclosure of his or her personal information to a third party. The customer shall have the option to limit the use of any personal information.

### Choice

Steadfast shall provide its customers with a choice to opt out of disclosure of their personal information to a third party or the use of the personal information for something other than it was originally collected.

### Onward Transfers

Before disclosing personal information to a third party, Steadfast shall notify the customer of the intended disclosure and shall provide the customer with the option to opt out of such disclosure.

### Security

Steadfast shall take reasonable steps to keep personal information secure to prevent loss of the information, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. When the customer submits sensitive information it is protected both online and offline by Steadfast. Any questions with respect to the security of Steadfast should be sent to: support@steadfast.net.

### Data Integrity

Steadfast shall use information collected for its relevant and intended purpose only. If there is any change of use of the personal information collected, Steadfast shall inform its customers and gain their approval before making such changes of the use of the personal information collected. Further, Steadfast shall take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information collected is accurate and reliable for its intended use.

### Access to Personal Information Received

Steadfast shall provide customers with reasonable access, as required by law, to their personal information in order to confirm that it is correct or to amend or delete inaccurate information. If a customer needs to correct, update, or remove personal information provided to Steadfast, the customer should contact Steadfast at: support@steadfast.net.

### Enforcement

Steadfast has established internal mechanisms to verify its ongoing adherence to its privacy policy, including the Safe Harbor Principles. Steadfast encourages individuals covered by this privacy policy to raise any concerns about our processing of personal information by contacting Steadfast at support@steadfast.net. After a complaint or concern is received, Steadfast will work internally and with the customer to resolve the issue. Further, Steadfast agrees to participate in the dispute resolution program provided by the European Data Protection Authorities or the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner.

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, NoZone, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact NoZone, Inc. at:

NoZone, Inc. / Steadfast Networks  
725 S Wells St  
8th Floor  
Chicago, IL 60607

NoZone, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by (your business name), please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.
